Blair and Lee Family Papers, 1640-1946 (bulk 1812-1920 ): Finding Aid C0614
Manuscripts Division
- Papers of Samuel Phillips Lee, 1772-1897; 1812-1897; 178 boxes
  - Documents, 1817-1897; 27 boxes
    - Personal, 1825-1897; 21 boxes
      - Receipts, 1834-1897 July; 10 boxes
        - Receipts, 1878 July-December; 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 6)
        - Receipts, 1879 January-July; 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 7)
        - Receipts, 1879 August-December; 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 8)
        - Receipts, 1880 January-July; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 1)
        - Receipts, 1880 August-December; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 2)
        - Receipts, 1881 January-August; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 3)
        - Receipts, 1881 September-December; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 4)
        - Receipts, 1882 January-May; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 5)
        - Receipts, 1882 June-December; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 6)
        - Receipts, 1883 January-May; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 7)
        - Receipts, 1883 June-December; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 8)
        - Receipts, 1884 January-June; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 1)
        - Receipts, 1884 July-December; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 2)
        - Receipts, 1885 January-May; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 3)
        - Receipts, 1885 June-December; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 4)
        - Receipts, 1886 January-August; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 5)
        - Receipts, 1886 September-December; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 6)
        - Receipts, 1887 January-June; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 1)
        - Receipts, 1887 July-December; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 2)
        - Receipts, 1888 January-April; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 3)
        - Receipts, 1888 May-September; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 4)
        - Receipts, 1888 October-December; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 5)
        - Receipts, 1889 January-July; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 6)
        - Receipts, 1889 August-December; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 7)
        - Receipts, 1890 January-August; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 8)
        - Receipts, 1890 September-December; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 9)
        - Receipts, 1891 January-May; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 1)
        - Receipts, 1891 June-September; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 2)
        - Receipts, 1891 October-December; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 3)
        - Receipts, 1892 January-April; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 4)
        - Receipts, 1892 May-August; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 5)
        - Receipts, 1892 September-December; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 6)
        - Receipts, 1893 January-May; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 7)
        - Receipts, 1893 June-August; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 8)
        - Receipts, 1893 September-December; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 9)
        - Receipts, 1895 January-May; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 1)
        - Receipts, 1894 June-August; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 2)
        - Receipts, 1894 September-December; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 3)
        - Receipts, 1895 January-May; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 4)
        - Receipts, 1895 June-August; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 5)
        - Receipts, 1895 September-December; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 6)
        - Receipts, 1896 January-March; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 7)
        - Receipts, 1896 April-July; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 8)
        - Receipts, 1896 August-December; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 9)
        - Receipts, 1897 January-July; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 10)
        - Receipts, undated; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 11)
      - Canceled Checks, 1844-1897; 6 boxes
        - Canceled Checks, 1844-1858; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 1)
        - Canceled Checks, 1859; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 2)
        - Canceled Checks, 1860; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 3)
        - Canceled Checks, 1861; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 4)
        - Canceled Checks, 1862; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 5)
        - Canceled Checks, 1863; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 6)
        - Canceled Checks, 1864; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 7)
        - Canceled Checks, 1865; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 8)
        - Canceled Checks, 1866; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 9)
        - Canceled Checks, 1867; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 10)
        - Canceled Checks, 1868; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 1)
        - Canceled Checks, 1869; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 2)
        - Canceled Checks, 1870; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 3)
        - Canceled Checks, 1871; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 4)
        - Canceled Checks, 1872; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 1)
        - Canceled Checks, 1873; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 2)
        - Canceled Checks, 1874; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 3)
        - Canceled Checks, 1875; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 4)
        - Canceled Checks, 1876; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 5)
        - Canceled Checks, 1877; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 6)
        - Canceled Checks, 1878; 1 folder (Box 156, Folder 7)
        - Canceled Checks, 1879; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 1)
        - Canceled Checks, 1880; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 2)
        - Canceled Checks, 1881; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 3)
        - Canceled Checks, 1882; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 4)
        - Canceled Checks, 1883; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 5)
        - Canceled Checks, 1884; 1 folder (Box 157, Folder 6)
        - Canceled Checks, 1885; 1 folder (Box 158, Folder 1)
        - Canceled Checks, 1886; 1 folder (Box 158, Folder 2)
        - Canceled Checks, 1887; 1 folder (Box 158, Folder 3)
        - Canceled Checks, 1888; 1 folder (Box 158, Folder 4)
        - Canceled Checks, 1889; 1 folder (Box 158, Folder 5)
        - Canceled Checks, 1890; 1 folder (Box 158, Folder 6)
        - Canceled Checks, 1891; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 1)
        - Canceled Checks, 1892; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 2)
        - Canceled Checks, 1893; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 3)
        - Canceled Checks, 1894; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 4)
        - Canceled Checks, 1895; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 5)
        - Canceled Checks, 1896; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 6)
        - Canceled Checks, 1897; 1 folder (Box 159, Folder 7)
      - Checkbooks, 1846-1897; 3 boxes 2 folders
        - Bank of the Metropolis, 1846-1848; 1 folder (Box 160, Folder 1)
        - Bank of Metropolis, Riggs & Co, 1859-1862; 1 folder (Box 160, Folder 2)
        - Riggs & Co, 1865-1897; 2 boxes 3 folders
          - Riggs & Co, 1865-1866 August; 1 folder (Box 160, Folder 3)
          - Riggs & Co, 1866 July-1868 June; 1 folder (Box 161, Folder 1)
          - Riggs & Co, 1868 June-1870 February; 1 folder (Box 161, Folder 2)
          - Riggs & Co, 1870 February-1872 April; 1 folder (Box 161, Folder 3)
          - Riggs & Co, 1872 April-1873 September; 1 folder (Box 161, Folder 4)
          - Riggs & Co, 1873 October-1877 January; 1 folder (Box 161, Folder 5)
          - Riggs & Co, 1877 February-1880 May; 1 folder (Box 162, Folder 1)
          - Riggs & Co, 1880 May-1883 April; 1 folder (Box 162, Folder 2)
          - Riggs & Co, 1883 April-1885 February; 1 folder (Box 162, Folder 3)
          - Riggs & Co, 1885 February-1888 January; 1 folder (Box 162, Folder 4)
          - Riggs & Co, 1888 February-1891 November; 1 folder (Box 162, Folder 5)
          - Riggs & Co, 1891 November-1895 October; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 1)
          - Riggs & Co, 1895 - 1897; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 2)
      - Account Books, 1848-1896; 4 folders
        - Account Books, 1877-1896; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 3)
        - Account Books, 1857-1868; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 4)
        - Account Books, 1868-1878; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 5)
        - Bank of the Metropolis, Bank of Commerce in New York, State Savings Association, 1848-1879; 1 folder (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Real Estate, 1817-1897; 6 boxes
      Contains documents regarding real estate in St. Louis, Mo., Kentucky, Maryland, and Washington, D.C., such as tax receipts, deeds, insurance policies, leases, memoranda of agreement, and general documents.
      - St. Louis, 1817-1897; 5 boxes
        - General, 1817-1897; 2 boxes
          - Abstracts, 1844-1855; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 1)
          - Agreements, 1849-1879; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 2)
          - Baggot & Haley: miscellaneous accounts, 1889-1897; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 3)
          - Bank of the State of Missouri: canceled notes, 1854-1855; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 4)
          - Contracts: Randolph and McLanahan, 1893; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 5)
          - Contracts: William L. Thirwell (re warehouse), 1855; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 6)
          - Deeds, 1818-1869; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 7)
          - Deeds and Deeds of Trust, 1872-1893; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 8)
          - Insurance policies, 1854-1888; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 9)
          - Lawsuits, 1879-1893; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 10)
          - Lawyers and agents: appointments, 1870-1872; 1 folder (Box 164, Folder 11)
          - Leases, 1849-1889; 2 folders (Box 165, Folder 1-2)
          - Miscellaneous documents, 1829-1878; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 3)
          - Miscellaneous real estate holdings, 1847-1880; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 4)
          - Notebook of St. Louis properties, 1849-1856; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 5)
          - Property maps, 1854-1878; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 6)
          - Records of St. Louis lots, 1849-1855; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 7)
          - Titles, 1817-1876; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 8)
          - Water licenses, 1892-1897; 1 folder (Box 165, Folder 9)
        - Tax Receipts, 1851-1897; 2 boxes
          - City of St. Louis, 1851-1897; 1 box
            - City of St. Louis, 1851-1860; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 1)
            - City of St. Louis, 1862-1866; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 2)
            - City of St. Louis, 1874-1877; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 3)
            - State, county, city and school, 1870-1876; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 4)
            - State, school and city, 1877-1885; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 5)
            - State, school and city, 1886-1897; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 6)
            - Extended new limits, 1856-1861; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 7)
            - Extended new limits, 1862-1865; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 8)
            - New limits, 1866; 1872-1877; 1 folder (Box 166, Folder 9)
          - Special tax bills, 1860-1897; 3 folders
            - Special tax bills, 1860-1889; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 1)
            - Special tax bills, 1890-1893; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 2)
            - Special tax bills, 1894-1897; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 3)
          - State, county, special, road and school, 1855-1857; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 4)
          - State, county and school, 1861-1866; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 5)
          - Bonhomme township, 1878-1888; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 6)
          - Central township, 1879-1895; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 7)
          - St. Ferdinand township, 1876-1896; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 8)
          - Townships 45 and 46, 1877-1895; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 9)
          - Miscellaneous, 1854-1884; 1 folder (Box 167, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1850-1896; 1 box
          - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1850-1859; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 1)
          - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1854-1859; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 2)
          - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1871-1878; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 3)
          - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1879; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 4)
          - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1880-1882; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 5)
          - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1883-1887; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 6)
          - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1888-1889; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 7)
          - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1890-1896; 1 folder (Box 168, Folder 8)
      - Maryland and Washington, D.C., 1845-1897; 1 box
        - Deeds, 1856; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 1)
        - Insurance policies, 1876-1891; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 2)
        - Leases, 1860-1896; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 3)
        - Memoranda of agreement, 1845-1897; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous, 1853-1896; 1 folder (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Naval Records, 1826-1892; 43 boxes
    Contains records and reports of naval vessels, during and after the Civil War, including the Brandywine, Young Rover, Vandalia, Newborn, Dolphin, and Severn.
    - Boarding Returns, 1862-1864 September; 20 boxes
      - Boarding Returns, 1862; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 January 3; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 January 4; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 January 10; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 January 17; 1 folder (Box 170, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 January 28; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 January 31; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 February 1-6; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 February 7; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 February 14; 1 folder (Box 171, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 February 21; 1 folder (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 February 22-26; 1 folder (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 February 28; 2 folders (Box 172, Folder 3-4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 March 5; 1 folder (Box 173, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 March 7; 2 folders (Box 173, Folder 2-3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 March 14; 1 folder (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 March 16; 1 folder (Box 173, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 March 19; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 March 21; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 March 24; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 March 28; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 March 29; 1 folder (Box 174, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 April 2; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 April 4; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 April 11; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 April 16; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 April 18; 1 folder (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 April 23; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 April 25; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 May 2; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 May 9; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 May 16; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 May 23; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 6)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 May 30; 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 7)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 June 4; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 June 6; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 June 13; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 June 20; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 June 26; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 June 27; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 6)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 July 4; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 7)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 July 10; 1 folder (Box 177, Folder 8)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 July 11; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 July 16; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 July 18; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 July 25; 1 folder (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 August 1; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 August 8; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 August 9; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 August 15; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 August 22; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 August 29; 1 folder (Box 179, Folder 6)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 September 5; 1 folder (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 September 12; 1 folder (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 September 19; 1 folder (Box 180, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 September 26; 1 folder (Box 180, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 October 3; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 October 10; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 October 17; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 October 24; 1 folder (Box 181, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 October 31; 2 folders (Box 182, Folder 1-2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 November 7; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 November 14; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 November 21; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 November 28; 1 folder (Box 182, Folder 6)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 December 5; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 December 12; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 December 19; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 December 26; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 December 27; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1863 December 28; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 6)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 January 2; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 January 9; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 January 16; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 January 23; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 January 30; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 February 6; 1 folder (Box 185, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 February 13; 1 folder (Box 185, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 February 20; 1 folder (Box 185, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 February 27; 1 folder (Box 185, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 March 5; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 March 12; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 March 19; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 March 26; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 April 2; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 April 9; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 April 16; 2 folders (Box 187, Folder 3-4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 April 23; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 April 30; 2 folders (Box 188, Folder 1-2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 May 7; 1 folder (Box 188, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 May 14; 1 folder (Box 188, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 May 21; 1 folder (Box 188, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 May 28; 1 folder (Box 188, Folder 6)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 June 4; 1 folder (Box 188, Folder 7)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 June 25; 1 folder (Box 188, Folder 8)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 July 2; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 1)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 July 9; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 2)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 July 16; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 3)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 July 23; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 4)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 July 30; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 5)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 August 6; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 6)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 August 13; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 7)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 August 14; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 8)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 August 20; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 9)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 August 27; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 10)
      - Boarding Returns, 1864 September 3-30; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1861-1872; 4 boxes
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1861; 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 1)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1862 January-September; 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 2)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1862 October -December 24; 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 3)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1864 December 26-December 31; 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 4)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1863 January-March; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 1)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1863 April-August; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 2)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1863 September -December 21; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 3)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1863 December 31; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 4)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1864 January -February 19; 1 folder (Box 192, Folder 1)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1864 February 20-28; 1 folder (Box 192, Folder 2)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1864 March -July 11; 1 folder (Box 192, Folder 3)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1864 July 12 - September; 1 folder (Box 192, Folder 4)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1870; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 1)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1871; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 2)
      - Lists of Officers and Crews, 1872; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Quarterly Returns, 1826-1872; 6 boxes
      - Quarterly Returns, 1861 October-December; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 1)
      - Quarterly Returns, 1826-1862; 3 folders
        - Quarterly Returns, 1st quarter, 1862 January-March; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 2)
        - Quarterly Returns, 3rd quarter, 1862; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 3)
        - Quarterly Returns, 4th quarter, 1862; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 4)
      - Quarterly Returns, 1863; 1 box 3 folders
        - Quarterly Returns, 1st quarter, 1863; 3 folders (Box 194, Folder 5-7)
        - Quarterly Returns, 2nd quarter, 1863; 3 folders (Box 195, Folder 1-3)
        - Quarterly Returns, 3rd quarter, 1863; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 4)
        - Quarterly Returns, 4th quarter, 1863; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 5)
      - Quarterly Returns, 1864; 2 boxes 3 folders
        - Quarterly Returns, 1st quarter, 1864; 1 box (Box 196)
        - Quarterly Returns, 2nd quarter, 1864; 1 box (Box 197)
        - Quarterly Returns, 3rd quarter, 1864; 3 folders (Box 198, Folder 1-3)
      - Quarterly Returns, 1871; 3 folders
        - Quarterly Returns, 2nd quarter, 1871; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 4)
        - Quarterly Returns, 3rd quarter, 1871; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 5)
        - Quarterly Returns, 4th quarter, 1871; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 6)
      - Quarterly Returns, 1872; 2 folders
        - Quarterly Returns, 1st quarter, 1872; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 7)
        - Quarterly Returns, 2nd quarter, 1872; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 8)
      - Quarterly Returns (Punishments), 1st quarter, 1864; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 1)
      - Quarterly Returns (Punishments), 3rd quarter, 1870; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 2)
      - Quarterly Returns (Punishments), 1871; 4 folders
        - Quarterly Returns (Punishments), 1st quarter, 1871; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 3)
        - Quarterly Returns (Punishments), 2nd quarter, 1871; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 4)
        - Quarterly Returns (Punishments), 3rd quarter, 1871; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 5)
        - Quarterly Returns (Punishments), 4th quarter, 1871; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 6)
      - Quarterly Returns (Punishments), 1872; 2 folders
        - Quarterly Returns (Punishments), 1st quarter, 1872; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 7)
        - Quarterly Returns (Punishments), 2nd quarter, 1872; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Morning Reports, 1860 November-1864 October 2; 2 boxes
      - Arrivals and Departures, 1863 January 2-1864 October 2; 4 folders
        - "Brandywine", 1863 January 2-1864 January 13; 2 folders
          - "Brandywine", 1863 January 2 - 1863 November 9; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 1)
          - "Brandywine", 1863 November 11 - 1864 January 13; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 2)
        - "Young Rover", 1864 January 28-October 2; 2 folders
          - "Young Rover", 1864 January 28 - 1864 June 30; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 3)